{
    "subject": "resource/Whitecraigs_railway_station",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Giffnock",
    "human_readable": "Whitecraigs railway station is located in Giffnock.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9324103593826294,
            "question": "Where is Whitecraigs railway station located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8451628684997559,
            "question": "What town is Whitecraigs railway station in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7451267838478088,
            "question": "Can you find a map of Whitecraigs railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7135062217712402,
            "question": "What type of transportation facility is Whitecraigs railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6438853144645691,
            "question": "Are there any nearby shops or restaurants to Whitecraigs railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6317058801651001,
            "question": "What are the train lines that serve Whitecraigs railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6076335310935974,
            "question": "Is there a ticket office at Whitecraigs railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5839217305183411,
            "question": "What is the history of Whitecraigs railway station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.469954252243042,
            "question": "Is Whitecraigs railway station in Scotland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3941124677658081,
            "question": "How often do trains depart from Whitecraigs railway station?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Whitecraigs railway station is located in Giffnock.",
            "html": "dbpedia_919_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Whitecraigs railway station in Scotland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_919_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Whitecraigs railway station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_919_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a ticket office at Whitecraigs railway station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_919_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_919_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_919_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_919_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_919_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_919_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_919_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_919_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_919_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_919_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_919_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that Whitecraigs railway station serves the Whitecraigs and Davieland areas, which are part of Giffnock. This information can be found in the first document."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents repeatedly mention that Whitecraigs Railway Station serves the areas of Whitecraigs and Davieland, which are part of Giffnock and Newton Mearns in East Renfrewshire. This supports the statement that Whitecraigs railway station is located in Giffnock."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}